KEHINDE SALAUDEEN

WEB DEVELOPER

080564995321

kehindesalaudeen222@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kehinde-salaudeen-39014b180/

hhttps://khenny-portfolio.netlify.app

PROFILE

I am an web developer with 3 years of experience in database administration and website design. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail. Always ready to learn and apply technical skills in proper deliverance of projects

SKILLS

- Web Design
- Network Engineer
- Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Html, CSS & Javascript
- ReactJS
- NodeJS

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Bayus College

2013 - 2018

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE

Computer Science

Caleb University

2018 - 2022

EXPERIENCE

IT SUPPORT STAFF

Lagos State Polythenic ICT

May - Oct 2021

- website design
- Built a wifi network the engireering department
- online classroom management
- Staff examination

WEB DEVELOP

Kenny Inc.

2018 - present

- Database administration and website design
- Built the logic for a streamlined ad-serving platform that scaled

Fullstack ReactJS & NodeJS Developer

IT MANAGER

Gemson Nursery & Primary School

2017 - present

- · Web Manager
- Supervision of sEducational institutions and online classroom management